<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>{{ title }}</title>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>
                {{ description }}
            </abstract>
            <purpose>{{ purpose }}</purpose>
        </descript>
    </idinfo>
    <dataIdInfo>
        <idPurp></idPurp>
        <idAbs></idAbs>
        <idCredit></idCredit>
        <idCitation>
            <resTitle>{{ title }}</resTitle>
        </idCitation>
        <searchKeys>
            <keyword></keyword>
        </searchKeys>
        <resConst>
            <Consts>
                <useLimit>NOT AN OFFICIAL Our Florida Reefs Product. Your use of
                    this map is at your own risk. This map is not intended to be
                    used for navigational purposes and is not intended to be
                    relied upon in situations where precise location information
                    is needed or where erroneous, inaccurate, or incomplete
                    location data may lead to death, personal injury, property
                    or environmental damage. Neither the Florida Department of
                    Environmental Protection (FDEP), Board of Trustees (BOT) of
                    the Internal Improvement Trust Fund of the State of Florida
                    nor any content providers, guarantees the accuracy,
                    completeness, or reliability of displayed data. In no event
                    will the FDEP or BOT of the Internal Improvement Trust Fund
                    of the State of Florida be liable for any damages whatsoever
                    (including, but not limited to, incidental, exemplary, and
                    consequential damages, lost profits, or damages resulting
                    from lost data or business interruption) resulting from the
                    use or inability to use this information, whether based on
                    warranty, contract, tort, or any other legal theory, and
                    whether or not the FDEP or BOT of the Internal Improvement
                    Trust Fund of the State of Florida are advised of the
                    possibility of such damages.
                </useLimit>
            </Consts>
        </resConst>
    </dataIdInfo>
</metadata>
